Hi guys, it's been a while but it's finally time for a new jumpsuit up video.
Did you miss them?
Today I have two jumpsuits I want to show you.
One in black with a lot of zippers and a red one.
Curious about that.
Both are from Kugler Fashion and both are like a kind of spandex wet look material
but before I talk too much in the beginning I'm just going to slip right into the first catsuit.
Okay, it fits really good.
That is the first impression.
I mean, the arms are really long, the legs are really long,
and the overall body length is also really good.
Big plus point.
I did not expect that, because normally most of the jumpsuits are too short somehow.
For me at least.
Let me check the mirror.
oh yeah it has a zipper in the crotch area or rather from the front to the back side and with
two zippers which is really handy if you want to go to the toilet for example and of course
i could close the zipper as well how does it look
i think now it looks like work overall like i want to go to do some construction work i don't
know why I think I prefer it open yeah that's better I kind of like these
zippers here they are nice design touch can I open them oh yeah apparently I can
open them and these ones they don't open okay that's kind of weird but anyway oh
Oh I also have slippers here I just realized so I can open to arm to get into it easier
although I did not have problems getting into this catsuit it was really stretchy
and it was really fast. Since I like to accentuate my waist area I always see if
I have a belt that fits to the catsuit. This one has a bit of a buckle so how does this work?
Like that.
I think it looks okay because the belt is not silver but this gunmetal metal
color here so it does work and yes it really adds something to the overall shape
because since the catsuit is so stretchy it does not shape the body in any way
alright I do have a second catsuit from the same brand and it's red or this kind
of orangey red. I'm very curious how you like it. You have to tell me in the comments but first I
will change into it.
I let your mind extend
I am like quicksand liquor
From my head
In my heart there's no place for you
And in my mind there's no space for you
All right it's red. It is a bit more orangey than I expected from the product
pictures but again really long arms really long legs big thumbs up for Kugler
for this design feature and I intently closed the zipper up here because it has
no collar that flaps around so that was the look I aimed for but I can also like
try to open it hmm I think for this one I really do prefer to close the collar
it's slightly see-through you can see my underwear and we have a belt with belt
holes and that is attached to the catsuit which is a nice design feature
since there are no decorative zippers this time just a zipper from the middle
to the back. And I have to say I don't get it why they put the zipper in like from the front
to the back but did not make it a three-way zipper. Because now if I want to go to the toilet
I have to unzip everything and get everything down. With the first one it was really good for
the three-way zipper but I don't know why they didn't do it here because they built the zipper in.
I wanted to pair it with my red heels but now in direct comparison you can see
that the catsuit is not really red so the color is a bit too different
oops I would not wear it out in a combination like that because it's just
not fitting enough but overall the catsuit fits good and I'm quite happy
with it but I have to say the winner for today for me is the black catsuit
simply it's yeah it's black no that's not the only reason it did fit a bit better in the body length and I like the design better and yeah it is a minus point that this isn't really red and that there's no three-way zipper so this is the winner and you should tell me in the comments which you preferred
I hope you enjoyed this one it was a quick no-brainer catsuit video for a change and if you
want to see more catsuit videos check out my playlist or all the other videos on my channel
I think most of them feature catsuits not all of them but most of them anyway I was filming all day
the videos for youtube if you want to support me then please check out my patreon and yeah
Like this channel. Yeah, you can also like this channel.
Subscribe to this channel, like this video, check out my Patreon.
I will see you in the next video. Have a nice bye.
I can't even talk anymore. It's time that I go and have dinner.
Bye.